 const question = [
    {
        question: 'Everything in React is a _____________ ',
        answers: ['Module', 'Component', 'Package', 'Class'],
        correct: 2
    },

    {
        question: 'In which directory React Components are saved?',
        answers: ['Inside js/components/', 'Inside vendor/components/', 'Inside external/components/', 'Inside vendor/'],
        correct: 1
    },    
    {
        question: 'How many elements does a react component return?',
        answers: ['2 Elements', '1 Element', 'Multiple Elements', 'None of the above'],
        correct: 3
    },    
    {
        question: 'What is state in React?',
        answers: ['A persistant storage.', 'An internal data store (object) of a component.', 'Redux store', 'None of the above'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'What is Babel?',
        answers: ['A transpiler', 'An interpreter', 'A Compiler', 'Both Compiler and Transpilar'],
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'What does the "webpack" command do?',
        answers: ['Transpiles all the Javascript down into one file', 'Runs react local development server', 'A module bundler', 'None of the above'],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'What port is the default where the webpack-dev-server will run?',
        answers: ['3000', '8080', '3306', '80'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'What is ReactJS?',
        answers: ['Server side Framework', 'User-interface framework', 'A Library for building interaction interfaces', 'None of the above'],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'What are the two ways that data gets handled in React?',
        answers: ['state & props', 'services & components', 'Redux', 'flux'],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'In React what is used to pass data to a component from outside?',
        answers: ['setState', 'render with arguments', 'props', 'PropTypes'],
        correct: 3
    }
]

export default question;